[
    {
        "main_category": "News & Events", 
        "question": "Why did the U.S Invade Iraq ?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "A small group of politicians believed strongly that the fact that Saddam Hussien remained in power after the first Gulf War was a signal of weakness to the rest of the world, one that invited attacks and terrorism. Shortly after taking power with George Bush in 2000 and after the attack on 9/11, they were able to use the terrorist attacks to justify war with Iraq on this basis and exaggerated threats of the development of weapons of mass destruction. The military strength of the U.S. and the brutality of Saddam's regime led them to imagine that the military and political victory would be relatively easy.", 
            "Because there is a lot of oil in Iraq.", 
            "It is tempting to say that the US invaded Iraq because it has lots of oil, but the US is not a country in a deep economic problem that capturing other country\u2019s oil is an actual need for survival. It is more likely that the Iraq invading Kuwait scenario would fall under that assumption.. I think that the US government has come to a conclusion that we are on the verge of a war of religions, or more likely ideologies. It would be presumptuous to try and determent a one cause to the coming war. . I think that the world wide spread of the media with its many forms (Cable, Satellite, Internet, etc.)  have pushed the Moslem regimes to the extreme, fearing that secularity and democratic influence is penetrating their country and will result in an up raising against them. One of the best way to maintain the power that you have and even gain more of it, is by hatred. When the common man is occupied hating an outside enemy, its hatred is kept out side the county and would not be directed towards the regime. . So- I believe that the US understands that the fanatic Moslem regimes have already started a war on the democratic world and now is the time to try a fight it.. . So why invade Iraq? Because it is a huge, week Moslem country that thought to be easy to defeat. . This is exactly the same reason why Afghanistan was first and Syria is next in line.", 
            "I think Yuval is pretty spot on. It's a proving ground and a focal point for terror activity that's not on American soil. And, because no one liked Saddam Hussein, no other countries (even in the Middle East) were about to rise up and join his side.. . Rabid speculation: now the Pentagon has a model that says it takes ~5 years, ~$200B and ~2,000 casualties to \"rebuild\" a dictatorship into a democracy. Who's next on the list?"
        ], 
        "answer": "A small group of politicians believed strongly that the fact that Saddam Hussien remained in power after the first Gulf War was a signal of weakness to the rest of the world, one that invited attacks and terrorism. Shortly after taking power with George Bush in 2000 and after the attack on 9/11, they were able to use the terrorist attacks to justify war with Iraq on this basis and exaggerated threats of the development of weapons of mass destruction. The military strength of the U.S. and the brutality of Saddam's regime led them to imagine that the military and political victory would be relatively easy.", 
        "id": "2020338"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Education & Reference", 
        "question": "How to get rid of a beehive?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Call an area apiarist.  They should be able to help you and would most likely remove them at no charge in exchange for the hive.  The bees have value and they now belong to you.", 
            "Don't try this yourself but this is what the old fashioned way is - done in some villages in other parts of the world.. . The guy who dismantles, wears a mask with holes at the eyes so he can see, carries a big sack with burning coals in it.  He also wraps his hands with thick cloths, carries an empty bag to collect the honey in it.. He then collects the honey in the empty bag, pulls the hive into the bag of coals.. . If he just wants to collect the honey, he would leave after collecting the honey - but the bag of coals is used to choke & burn the bees if he wanted to get rid of the hive.. . That's a bit like coding in COBOL & assembly :)"
        ], 
        "answer": "Call an area apiarist.  They should be able to help you and would most likely remove them at no charge in exchange for the hive.  The bees have value and they now belong to you.", 
        "id": "2874684"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Society & Culture", 
        "question": "Why don't European restaurants serve water?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "There's a general belief in Europe (and in fact elsewhere in the world, such as China) that it's unhealthy to drink water with a meal because it dilutes the digestive juices. Wine is OK because it stimulates digestion, and mineral waters are also considered digestives.. . In general, Europeans are much more concerned with the digestive process than Americans.", 
            "I'd like to take a different approach in answering this. I think geographical location and higher availability of other drinks probably is a bigger reason that water is not consumed as much by people in certain regions, including Europe. I believe and many visitors have commented that children drink less water and more soda in USA.  This is primarily due to the fact that soda companies advertise a lot, making it more attractive. Secondly, SODA IS ATTRACTIVE, and according to a few medical experts it's even addictive (yes, caffeine is addictive to some extent).  . . Secondly the cold weather in upper northern hemisphere in general is more of a reason that ppl drink less water and more of other drinks.  For example if you are from a tropical country or from a very humid place, you would probably & naturally  be drinking more water rather than if you are from   a country like Austria, Switzerland, Denmark, Finland.. . Another reason is that people being less immune to impure water (like tap water) and being more dependent on bottled water makes the water less affordable and less available.  If you need to pay  extra or need to work harder to get the commodity, you may resort to cheaper commodity or a near by commodity.. . Another reason I also feel is the commute using Cars rather than walking or cycling.  If you walk more to commute (like walk to train stations, walk a few blocks to get groceries, etc.) then you are more likely to drink water when compared to driving to every place you go and exert yourself much less.  In many other countries people walk, walk and walk for several small things.. . Lack of education and awareness is also a reason for not consuming enough water. Not many people (except for few educated ones)know that 80% of our body is water.  Even if they knew, ppl forget that fact easily and resort to \"other drinks\".. . There are simply several reasons or combination of reasons for not consuming enough water by the people in general.. . Finally, after having said all this,. Beer Happens!"
        ], 
        "answer": "There's a general belief in Europe (and in fact elsewhere in the world, such as China) that it's unhealthy to drink water with a meal because it dilutes the digestive juices. Wine is OK because it stimulates digestion, and mineral waters are also considered digestives.. . In general, Europeans are much more concerned with the digestive process than Americans.", 
        "id": "4193114"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Cars & Transportation", 
        "question": "Why hybrid cars gas mileage is better in city ?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "hybrid cars save energy in two ways: 1.by storing energy from the breaks2.by engaging the gas motor only in it's most effective work RPM meaning that the system will engage the gas motor mostly at coursing speed (close to the most efficient motor RPM)Having said the above, driving in the city almost never gets you to the efficient RPM.Also- it is true that the same energy that is being stored in the cars' battery needed to be generated by chemic energy. The cool thing about it is that the pollution can be outside of the city and not in the city. (Like in San Francisco, the electric buses generate the same pollution as a gas buses it is just not in the city.You can also add that electric engines are much quieter then gas engines.So- all in all- I the hybrid benefits are more visible in city driving", 
            "The gas mileage for some hybrids is better in the city because they spend more time using their electric motor instead of their gas engine.  Most hybrids have battery packs which are charged by what is called \"generative breaking\".  Instead of slowing down with traditional braking, these cars store some of the energy from braking into a battery pack.  Then when the light changes and the car moves again, the energy stored in the battery can be used to move the car, or assist the engine in moving the car.. . In the city this effect can be more pronounced because of more frequent stopping and starting.", 
            "There are the two reasons mentioned already - using the energy from the breaks and using the gas engine only when it can work efficiently.. . One more thing to note is that for several cars, the hybrid model of a car has a smaller gas engine than the regular models (e.g. for Honda Civic the gas engine for the hybrid model is 1.3L, which is not available in the regular models). So even without the other things, this engine will get better gas mileage than the larger engines."
        ], 
        "answer": "hybrid cars save energy in two ways: 1.by storing energy from the breaks2.by engaging the gas motor only in it's most effective work RPM meaning that the system will engage the gas motor mostly at coursing speed (close to the most efficient motor RPM)Having said the above, driving in the city almost never gets you to the efficient RPM.Also- it is true that the same energy that is being stored in the cars' battery needed to be generated by chemic energy. The cool thing about it is that the pollution can be outside of the city and not in the city. (Like in San Francisco, the electric buses generate the same pollution as a gas buses it is just not in the city.You can also add that electric engines are much quieter then gas engines.So- all in all- I the hybrid benefits are more visible in city driving", 
        "id": "1908421"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Science & Mathematics", 
        "question": "Can someone explain the theory of e=mc2?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "In general it means that in a very high speed (also apply for low speed but hard to measure) , a Mass turns into Energy and vise versa. The conversion rate is C2 (C square).", 
            "I think an expansion on the answer from the previous person may be in order.... . E=mc^2 or \"energy equals mass times the speed of light squared\" was Einstein's breakthrough theory on the relationship between energy and matter. It showed that matter is indeed \"contained\" energy, and allowed that energy to be calculated.. . This relationship was critical to the development of atomic energy as it allowed physicists to determine the amount of energy that would be released because they could calculate the energy of the atom (from its mass) and compare it to the energy of its parts (protons, neutrons & electrons) by their masses. The difference was the energy contained in the binding of the parts, which as we know now, is huge."
        ], 
        "answer": "In general it means that in a very high speed (also apply for low speed but hard to measure) , a Mass turns into Energy and vise versa. The conversion rate is C2 (C square).", 
        "id": "3608897"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Education & Reference", 
        "question": "For colIege admission, is it better to take AP classes and get Bs or easy classes and get As?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "I used to work in a college admissions office for a major university and they used a specific formula for calculating GPAs. They did this to put everyone on an even playing field - so that high schools that don't weight AP classes differently would be measured the same as those that do. Though I don't remember the specific calculation anymore, I definitely remember that AP classes were given a higher score. I'd suggest you take the AP class and try for the best grade you can get - because ultimately it'll be weighted higher at the college/university you are interested in, giving you a better chance of getting in!", 
            "Most colleges look at GPA and class rank.  Also, most high schools multiply earned AP gpa by a multiplier to reflect additional difficulty.  For instance, a B in an AP class in my school was a 3.96 vs a 4.0 for an A in a standard class.  In that case, the AP class is probably better.  I'd like to think that more selective colleges take a more holistic approach to admissions, though I have no evidence of this, as I got a budget priced state school education.  (and a darn good one at that!)"
        ], 
        "answer": "I used to work in a college admissions office for a major university and they used a specific formula for calculating GPAs. They did this to put everyone on an even playing field - so that high schools that don't weight AP classes differently would be measured the same as those that do. Though I don't remember the specific calculation anymore, I definitely remember that AP classes were given a higher score. I'd suggest you take the AP class and try for the best grade you can get - because ultimately it'll be weighted higher at the college/university you are interested in, giving you a better chance of getting in!", 
        "id": "2175566"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Politics & Government", 
        "question": "Why didn't anyone send more buses to the Superdome earlier?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "I don't have an article, but I was listening to NPR last night, and the commentator was saying the evacuation was really bungled due to an organization and communication problem. No one took charge and said, hey I'm running the show, get 2000 buses and send them down, because no one felt they were in charge. FEMA, State & local police, National Guard, all were not sure what the other guys were doing and so waited for overall direction, which never really came.", 
            "Rising gas prices and the dwindling value of the US dollar.", 
            "I would be very surprise if the senator will be reelected. This should have being his/her job to \u201cshout\u201d as hard as she could and then a bit more- she is the communicator to all federal issues and she failed miserably. The senator should have called to all the near by cities/states and ask for rescue buses, call the army/national guard to have an thousand of transport aircraft to be able to take as much people as possible to near by states. . . No doubt, FEMA has a lot to be blame too, but I think that locally that was the senator job to manage and to raise all the red flags."
        ], 
        "answer": "I don't have an article, but I was listening to NPR last night, and the commentator was saying the evacuation was really bungled due to an organization and communication problem. No one took charge and said, hey I'm running the show, get 2000 buses and send them down, because no one felt they were in charge. FEMA, State & local police, National Guard, all were not sure what the other guys were doing and so waited for overall direction, which never really came.", 
        "id": "2071476"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Science & Mathematics", 
        "question": "how do Elephants communicate?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "There make very low frequency sounds that we cannot hear. They also make sounds that we do hear and it is because they what other animals to hear it.", 
            "To expand on the previous answer... these low frequency sounds are called subsonic or infrasounds. A variety of animals hear in this range, such as elephants, whales and alligators. Your home subwoofer works on the same principle. Big benefit of subsonics is that they travel over long distances well."
        ], 
        "answer": "There make very low frequency sounds that we cannot hear. They also make sounds that we do hear and it is because they what other animals to hear it.", 
        "id": "3995851"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Pets", 
        "question": "why does dogs, which have an excellent smell sense, needs to stuck their nose into whatever they", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "its expected, as the concentration of the molecules that have the scent they are trying to get rapidly fades away with distance. . . They can get a sense that something is there, but when they are very close, probably they will have even more information: how long that smell is there, how many different scents are there, etc.", 
            "Dogs are morons. They need to really really concentrate on a specific scent to understand / comprehend the smell. Their peabrains are not equal to their superior olfactory senses.", 
            "Dogs experience the world through smell. Their range of vision is not as good as ours, and they rely on their sense of smell to find food, shelter, and their mates and packs.. Dogs sniff and sniff and sniff because they enjoy it. Just as you sit down to read a good book, a dog goes on a walk and smells his environment. Paul Auster referred to it as \"the symphony of smells\". It's how they interact with the world, and without an opportunity to go out and sniff, a dog can actually get quite bored!"
        ], 
        "answer": "its expected, as the concentration of the molecules that have the scent they are trying to get rapidly fades away with distance. . . They can get a sense that something is there, but when they are very close, probably they will have even more information: how long that smell is there, how many different scents are there, etc.", 
        "id": "1128194"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Food & Drink", 
        "question": "How to boil lobster?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Fill a large pot with 1/4 full of water or just enough to cover your lobster and add a generous handful of salt. When it comes to a boil, put the lobster in the pot head first. Then boil for 18 for the first pound and 10 minutes more for each additional pound.  For lobsters over 7 pounds, 8 minutes per additional pound is enough.", 
            "Here's how:. . You'll need the following:. . large deep pot. long tongs. live lobsters. boiling salted water. melted butter. . Bring salted water to a rolling boil. Using long tongs, quickly but carefully lower live lobsters into the boiling water. Simmer for about 10 minutes, or until lobsters are bright red.  Serve with melted butter for dipping."
        ], 
        "answer": "Fill a large pot with 1/4 full of water or just enough to cover your lobster and add a generous handful of salt. When it comes to a boil, put the lobster in the pot head first. Then boil for 18 for the first pound and 10 minutes more for each additional pound.  For lobsters over 7 pounds, 8 minutes per additional pound is enough.", 
        "id": "1274254"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Science & Mathematics", 
        "question": "what are the base colors?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "There are two kinds of primary colors:  those you get by combining light (these are called \"additive\") and those you get by mixing pigments (these are called \"subtractive\").  As many computer users know, the additive colors are red, green, and blue.  Traditionally, the subtractive colors were red, yellow, and blue.  But more technically, they are magenta, yellow, and cyan (a kind of blue).", 
            "Red, blue and yellow."
        ], 
        "answer": "There are two kinds of primary colors:  those you get by combining light (these are called \"additive\") and those you get by mixing pigments (these are called \"subtractive\").  As many computer users know, the additive colors are red, green, and blue.  Traditionally, the subtractive colors were red, yellow, and blue.  But more technically, they are magenta, yellow, and cyan (a kind of blue).", 
        "id": "629558"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Food & Drink", 
        "question": "Can you give advice on how to pick watermelons?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Knock on the watermelon (just like you would knock on a door).  If it sounds hollow, it's ripe.", 
            "Pick one up and flick it with your index finger. If it sounds hollow and echos or vibrates a little, it's good."
        ], 
        "answer": "Knock on the watermelon (just like you would knock on a door).  If it sounds hollow, it's ripe.", 
        "id": "2142220"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Food & Drink", 
        "question": "What meats are suited for a slow cooker?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Tougher cuts or meat with more fat. These cuts will stay juicy and become tender from the long, slow cooking time. Pork loin is not the best choice for slow cookers.", 
            "Beef and pork are probably most suited as they are tougher."
        ], 
        "answer": "Tougher cuts or meat with more fat. These cuts will stay juicy and become tender from the long, slow cooking time. Pork loin is not the best choice for slow cookers.", 
        "id": "4264323"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Society & Culture", 
        "question": "Why is it considered unlucky to open an umbrella indoors?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Possibly because African royalty used umbrellas as protection from the sun, and opening one in the shade was considered an insult to the sun god. Opening it indoors was also taboo.", 
            "Some people believe that if there is a sick person indoors, opening an umbrella indoors will make them sicker. Strangely, it is not considered to bring an already open umbrella in and leaving it open to dry.. Like many superstitions, like walking under a ladder or breaking a mirror, it probably boils down to safety and common sense. Walk under a ladder and you could knock it and the person on it down. Open an umbrella inside and you could break something or poke somebody's eye out!"
        ], 
        "answer": "Possibly because African royalty used umbrellas as protection from the sun, and opening one in the shade was considered an insult to the sun god. Opening it indoors was also taboo.", 
        "id": "1166941"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Food & Drink", 
        "question": "What is bubble tea and what's in it?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Bubble tea is a drink that is a mix of tea, milk, sugar, and giant black tapioca balls. The \"bubble\" refers to the foam created by shaking the freshly brewed tea with ice.  It is also called boba tea, tapioca tea, boba nai cha, pearl tea, milk tea, bubble drink, zhen zhu nai cha, tapioca pearl drink, momi, momi milk tea, QQ, etc.", 
            "Bubble drinks are cool, refreshing, and a sweet drink with tapioca pearls sitting on the bottom of a clear cup.  The drink is made with fresh fruits, milk, and crushed ice to create a healthy milk shake. You can also find drinks that are made of powdered flavoring, creamer, water, and crushed ice. And if you like it like the Asians do, the cool drink usually includes a healthy tea, infused by a flavoring.  When adding flavor, the tea and flavoring needed to be shaken well for a good all around taste. This formed bubbles in the drink, which came to be known as \"Bubble Tea.\""
        ], 
        "answer": "Bubble tea is a drink that is a mix of tea, milk, sugar, and giant black tapioca balls. The \"bubble\" refers to the foam created by shaking the freshly brewed tea with ice.  It is also called boba tea, tapioca tea, boba nai cha, pearl tea, milk tea, bubble drink, zhen zhu nai cha, tapioca pearl drink, momi, momi milk tea, QQ, etc.", 
        "id": "3615734"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Society & Culture", 
        "question": "Why do we only drink eggnog during Christmas?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Eggnog is a popular wintertime drink.  We do not serve eggnog only during Christmas.  It is also popular on New Year's day and some serve it on Thanksgiving.", 
            "Eggnog has been the traditional Christmas drink.  It's a nice drink for cold weather. :)"
        ], 
        "answer": "Eggnog is a popular wintertime drink.  We do not serve eggnog only during Christmas.  It is also popular on New Year's day and some serve it on Thanksgiving.", 
        "id": "1904608"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Food & Drink", 
        "question": "What's the difference between European butter and regular butter?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "European butter has a higher percentage of butterfat.  That's why they smell so yummy, e.g. plugras.", 
            "My Irish friend swears Irish butter tastes better than any other kind of butter. Something about the way the cows are raised there--green pastures, fresh Irish air...", 
            "Also, most European butters are unsalted"
        ], 
        "answer": "European butter has a higher percentage of butterfat.  That's why they smell so yummy, e.g. plugras.", 
        "id": "3349006"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Science & Mathematics", 
        "question": "If light travels faster than sound, then why do we hear sound first and then see picture when we turn on TV ?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "In most cases, the television needs to 'warm-up' its cathode ray tube before it can start to display an image on the screen.. . The audio coils require much less charging time and can start to emit sound sooner than we can see the image on the television.", 
            "With a standard CRT base television, there is a small delay in the time it takes for the guns to warm up to generate a picture on the television.  There is no warm up time involved in the speakers of your television, thus there is no picture at all for a brief period of while the sound is audible."
        ], 
        "answer": "In most cases, the television needs to 'warm-up' its cathode ray tube before it can start to display an image on the screen.. . The audio coils require much less charging time and can start to emit sound sooner than we can see the image on the television.", 
        "id": "3464482"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Business & Finance", 
        "question": "How do I write a resume?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "resume writing can be tricky because not only is it important to be detailed when describing skills and work experience, but it is also advantageous to balance this with brevity. be concise and to the point while packing your resume full of key information that presents your strengths as a candidate for employment.. keep it simple, and make sure that formatting doesn't take away from a neatly streamlined and cogent resume.. below is a link to hotjobs' resume tips, which i found extremely helpful in this process.", 
            "Check out the resume section under the link listed as source.. There is no \"standard\" one resume, its all about your strengths and goals. . Be as clear and positive as possible, highlight your accomplishments and stay focused on your goals.. I also recommend discussing your resume with people you trust before sending it out the first time to get feedback. . Good luck!"
        ], 
        "answer": "resume writing can be tricky because not only is it important to be detailed when describing skills and work experience, but it is also advantageous to balance this with brevity. be concise and to the point while packing your resume full of key information that presents your strengths as a candidate for employment.. keep it simple, and make sure that formatting doesn't take away from a neatly streamlined and cogent resume.. below is a link to hotjobs' resume tips, which i found extremely helpful in this process.", 
        "id": "299316"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Education & Reference", 
        "question": "Why do men wear neckties?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "I believe it originated in Croatia sometime in the middle ages where it was primarily worn by men to show allegiance to their King. It seems to have gained popularity in France where the French form for Croatia resulted in them being called 'cravat'. Details in the article.", 
            "Because it's fashionable and it won't go out of style.  There are different designs but these designs are based on the classic ones."
        ], 
        "answer": "I believe it originated in Croatia sometime in the middle ages where it was primarily worn by men to show allegiance to their King. It seems to have gained popularity in France where the French form for Croatia resulted in them being called 'cravat'. Details in the article.", 
        "id": "2141961"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "News & Events", 
        "question": "How does China view North Korea's claimed nuclear weapons capability?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "China is more concerned with threat from US or Japan than North Korea.  Besides, both India and Pakistan have nuclear weapon already and are close to China as well.  But it's hardly a big concern for China people.", 
            "chinese people are busy making money and don't want to waste time on these issues anymore, man. who dares to use nuclear weapons?"
        ], 
        "answer": "China is more concerned with threat from US or Japan than North Korea.  Besides, both India and Pakistan have nuclear weapon already and are close to China as well.  But it's hardly a big concern for China people.", 
        "id": "2586073"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Education & Reference", 
        "question": "Why are handicapped bathroom stalls always built at the end of the restroom?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Presumably because they tend to be longer/bigger to accommodate extra space, and the most efficient place to put a larger stall is at the end of the room. (It would be in the way if it were in the middle.)", 
            "Because you need to have a walled corner to put those bars on for holding onto."
        ], 
        "answer": "Presumably because they tend to be longer/bigger to accommodate extra space, and the most efficient place to put a larger stall is at the end of the room. (It would be in the way if it were in the middle.)", 
        "id": "2796007"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Cars & Transportation", 
        "question": "What's the ugliest car on the road?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "The Pontiac Aztek.  Cars like the Scion xB and Toyota Prius are polarizing cars but they sell in big numbers and hit their targets.  The Aztek was frighteningly faithful to its concept vehicle and answered a question that no one asked: what would happen if we put a sloping rear window and regular doors on a minivan?  Heads should have rolled at GM for that decision, the sales for the Aztek have been abysmal since its launch.", 
            "It's the car Xzibit takes into West Coast Customs before he pimps their ride."
        ], 
        "answer": "The Pontiac Aztek.  Cars like the Scion xB and Toyota Prius are polarizing cars but they sell in big numbers and hit their targets.  The Aztek was frighteningly faithful to its concept vehicle and answered a question that no one asked: what would happen if we put a sloping rear window and regular doors on a minivan?  Heads should have rolled at GM for that decision, the sales for the Aztek have been abysmal since its launch.", 
        "id": "701750"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Food & Drink", 
        "question": "Why do people put salt around the glass when drinking Margarita?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Salt is traditionally added to the rim of the glass to provide a sharp contrast in flavor to better experience the drink as a whole.. The difference in the salt and the sugar content in the alcohol helps to stimulate all of your tastebuds, which are divided into sectors based on the type of sensation.. Take caution to not over-salt the rim of the glass and thus coat only the outside portion of the rim around 1/4\"... getting salt on the inside of the glass risks modifying the flavor of the drink.", 
            "The salt cancels out the unpleasant flavor in Tequila.  Its the same as when people are doing Tequila shots, \"lick the salt, down the shot, suck the lemon\".", 
            "I believe it adds to the taste - changes the bite of the tequila. Kind of how people add lemon to their water or milk to their coffee. Just a guess..."
        ], 
        "answer": "Salt is traditionally added to the rim of the glass to provide a sharp contrast in flavor to better experience the drink as a whole.. The difference in the salt and the sugar content in the alcohol helps to stimulate all of your tastebuds, which are divided into sectors based on the type of sensation.. Take caution to not over-salt the rim of the glass and thus coat only the outside portion of the rim around 1/4\"... getting salt on the inside of the glass risks modifying the flavor of the drink.", 
        "id": "291061"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "What is CGI?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Common Gateway Interface (CGI) is an important World Wide Web technology that enables a client web browser to request data from a program executed on the Web server. CGI specifies a standard for passing data between the client and the program.. . An aim of CGI is to be language-neutral, though Perl is often associated with it.", 
            "Common Gateway Interface", 
            "depends on the context; this is \"programming\" and yes, CGI is the above-mentioned definitions, of course; but is also often used as \"Computer Generated Imagery\" when referring to the results of software used to make special effects in media.. . just thought I'd throw that in..."
        ], 
        "answer": "Common Gateway Interface (CGI) is an important World Wide Web technology that enables a client web browser to request data from a program executed on the Web server. CGI specifies a standard for passing data between the client and the program.. . An aim of CGI is to be language-neutral, though Perl is often associated with it.", 
        "id": "599506"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Games & Recreation", 
        "question": "Why can't I get used to console-style controls in FPS games?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "I suggest going back to your computer for FPS. Console controls are not well-suited to FPS style gameplay. The only console that will truly be able to pull this off well is the Nintendo Revolution (which will come out next year).", 
            "I have to disagree with the previous answer. I think it really comes down to what you're most familiar with. Personally, I never really got into PC gaming as heavily as I did console gaming. As such, I find a controller much more natural than a keyboard and mouse; much as I'd expect a PC gamer to find a controller awkward and clumsy.. . The keyboard and mouse have many a lot of advantages, and if you pitted a controller-player against a keyboard-and-mouse-player, the controller-player would be at a distinct disadvantage. . . All in all though, console makers and game developers have done a fantastic job of mapping FPS controls to hand-held controllers. It just takes practice. That and you may want to consider adjusting the look sensitivity for your controller.. . But I wouldn't worry too much. With the USB ports on the newer consoles that have hit (Xbox 360) or will be hitting (PS3) the market, you can expect to see some keyboards and mice coming out to appeal to PC gamers.. . As for the Nintendo Revolution's controller, I'm skeptical of how well it will work in practice. It's a great concept, but I think it will prove difficult to execute successfully enough not to become a niche feature. That, coupled with Nintendo's limited FPS library and lack of support from some of the industry's leading FPS developers doesn't give me an optimistic picture of the Revolution being the place to be in terms of getting an FPS fix.", 
            "Try inverting your controller if you haven't.  Halo and doom 3 are backwards compared to your mouse.  On the console pushing the look stick forward points your head up, while pushing the mouse forward points your head down.  . . Consoles are backwards by default.  And too all you console geeks out there who don't believe me.... . Put your hand on the top of your head.  Now push forward.  Are you looking down or up?"
        ], 
        "answer": "I suggest going back to your computer for FPS. Console controls are not well-suited to FPS style gameplay. The only console that will truly be able to pull this off well is the Nintendo Revolution (which will come out next year).", 
        "id": "1528314"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Health", 
        "question": "Why are blueberries so good for your health?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Blueberries are high in anti-oxidants. Also, they are low in saturated fat, cholesterol and sodium. They are a good source of dietary fiber, vitamins C and K and manganese.", 
            "Blueberries are very low in fat and sodium and a source of Vitamins A and C, potassium and folate.  Blueberries are also disease fighters.. . http://www.blueberry.org/health.htm", 
            "Laboratory rats whose diets are supplemented with blueberries have been shown to be healthier in many different respects, but it will take a lot more research to figure out all of the reasons why. .  . According to Dr Weil, \"The anthocyanins they contain (the pigments that make them blue) are potent antioxidants.\"  Of course these days \"contains potent antioxidants\" often means \"we have no idea how it works.\"  We found out a long time ago that many healthy fresh foods contain vitamin C, which truly enough is healthy because it's a \"potent antioxidant,\" but that didn't mean that we had the whole story.  Fresh fruits are still (demonstrably) better for you than taking a vitamin C pill, and a lot of research is being done to figure out why that's so.  Every time they find something that might play a role, they give it a fancy name like \"anthocyanins\" or \"bioflavonoids,\" but nobody knows how many fancy names stand between us and truly unlocking the mystery of blueberries. .  . That means that, for now, there's nothing to do but relax and enjoy what nature made us. .  . <3"
        ], 
        "answer": "Blueberries are high in anti-oxidants. Also, they are low in saturated fat, cholesterol and sodium. They are a good source of dietary fiber, vitamins C and K and manganese.", 
        "id": "2472154"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Travel", 
        "question": "Why do we drive on the parkway...?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Parkway doesn't refer to parking a car, it refers to the greenery or parkland landscape next to the road.. . The driveway isn't necessarily meant for parking a car, though many people do. It is the path you drive up to get to the house.", 
            "Because we park in the driveway."
        ], 
        "answer": "Parkway doesn't refer to parking a car, it refers to the greenery or parkland landscape next to the road.. . The driveway isn't necessarily meant for parking a car, though many people do. It is the path you drive up to get to the house.", 
        "id": "780477"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Education & Reference", 
        "question": "What does \"buck naked\" mean?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Dating from the 1920's the expression buck naked commonly means completely or totally naked or without a \"stitch\" (as opposed to partially naked). Synonyms include \"bare naked\", \"buck-arse naked\", and \"butt naked\" (also spelled, facetiously, \"butt nekkid\"). In the South, \"buck naked\" or \"butt naked\" means not in your house, out looking for trouble on Saturday night and wearing no clothes.", 
            "That you are very naked."
        ], 
        "answer": "Dating from the 1920's the expression buck naked commonly means completely or totally naked or without a \"stitch\" (as opposed to partially naked). Synonyms include \"bare naked\", \"buck-arse naked\", and \"butt naked\" (also spelled, facetiously, \"butt nekkid\"). In the South, \"buck naked\" or \"butt naked\" means not in your house, out looking for trouble on Saturday night and wearing no clothes.", 
        "id": "178068"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Society & Culture", 
        "question": "What is the meaning of life?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "aproximately 16.  it is 42 less the universe and everything.", 
            "Well, from wich perspective do you look at it? In my opinion, physical reality incarnations are done for the purpouse of spiritual growth...\"body is a car, soul is a driver, YOU\". Aside from that, I believe all is devine, in other words, all is god, source, as some say it. I also believe that each seek's to reunite with source... :) Take Care, Love and Light"
        ], 
        "answer": "Well, from wich perspective do you look at it? In my opinion, physical reality incarnations are done for the purpouse of spiritual growth...\"body is a car, soul is a driver, YOU\". Aside from that, I believe all is devine, in other words, all is god, source, as some say it. I also believe that each seek's to reunite with source... :) Take Care, Love and Light", 
        "id": "957372"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Cars & Transportation", 
        "question": "Why won't drivers use thier turn signals?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Simple math: one hand on cell phone, other hand on coffee mug, right foot on gas pedal, left knee for steering.  What do you want them to use to activate the turn signal?", 
            "> Why give those drivers the courtesy of the signal when in return they just rob you of your opportunity?. . To avoid an accident.", 
            "Contrary to the lazy theory...  What's the common driver's reaction to someone in an adjacent lane signaling to come into their lane?  They speed up and close the gap.  Why give those drivers the courtesy of the signal when in return they just rob you of your opportunity?"
        ], 
        "answer": "Simple math: one hand on cell phone, other hand on coffee mug, right foot on gas pedal, left knee for steering.  What do you want them to use to activate the turn signal?", 
        "id": "3666942"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Health", 
        "question": "Why do women get PMS?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Premenstrual syndrome (PMS) is a group of symptoms related to the menstrual cycle. PMS is linked to changes in the endocrine system, which produces hormones that control the menstrual cycle. Medical experts don't fully understand the chain of events that causes premenstrual symptoms to be severe in some women and not in others. The one direct cause that is known to affect some women is genetic: Many women with PMS have a close family member with a history of PMS.", 
            "it's nature's way of making sure we don't bottle up our frustrations."
        ], 
        "answer": "Premenstrual syndrome (PMS) is a group of symptoms related to the menstrual cycle. PMS is linked to changes in the endocrine system, which produces hormones that control the menstrual cycle. Medical experts don't fully understand the chain of events that causes premenstrual symptoms to be severe in some women and not in others. The one direct cause that is known to affect some women is genetic: Many women with PMS have a close family member with a history of PMS.", 
        "id": "2519839"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Education & Reference", 
        "question": "What should you do when you apply to a university and you get put on a waiting list?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Don't panic, sometimes they'll tuck you in at the last minute.  Also, if you really need to get into that particular university, you need to wait it out.  Or you can attempt to dig out some additional proof of how wonderful you are and beg/cajole to re-apply.  No matter what happens, ensure you have at least another university to fall back on.", 
            "Talk to the admissions officer and find out if you can improve your chance of getting in; be polite but persistent, and do not pester."
        ], 
        "answer": "Don't panic, sometimes they'll tuck you in at the last minute.  Also, if you really need to get into that particular university, you need to wait it out.  Or you can attempt to dig out some additional proof of how wonderful you are and beg/cajole to re-apply.  No matter what happens, ensure you have at least another university to fall back on.", 
        "id": "675709"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "Why doesn't Yahoo mail beta support SafarI on Mac?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Because Firefox and IE comprise the majority of the browser market by far.  Safari support is in the works.", 
            "Because Yahoo! support of Macs sucks ass.  Compared Y!Messenger on Windows to the Mac version lately?"
        ], 
        "answer": "Because Firefox and IE comprise the majority of the browser market by far.  Safari support is in the works.", 
        "id": "2802889"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "News & Events", 
        "question": "What happened to the missing 18.5 minutes on the Watergate tapes?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "President Nixon's secretary, Rose Mary Woods, said she may have erased several minutes of the tapes when she \"accidentally\" pressed record while answering the phone.  There's a famous picture of her showing how this might have happened (included in link below), but the picture actually makes it look even more unlikely that it was an accident.. . Most people believe that the tapes were erased intentionally, either by Woods or someone else.  No one knows what's on them.", 
            "Nobody knows (yet).  In 2003 the National  Archives decided that no technology exists to restore the missing minutes.  The tapes are still being preserved and it is hoped that in the future the missing minutes will be restored."
        ], 
        "answer": "President Nixon's secretary, Rose Mary Woods, said she may have erased several minutes of the tapes when she \"accidentally\" pressed record while answering the phone.  There's a famous picture of her showing how this might have happened (included in link below), but the picture actually makes it look even more unlikely that it was an accident.. . Most people believe that the tapes were erased intentionally, either by Woods or someone else.  No one knows what's on them.", 
        "id": "645771"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Education & Reference", 
        "question": "How do I convert metric to U.S units?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "I recommend tables of conversion factors or units.  An example is one provided by Wikipedia for free.", 
            "Google does conversions very nicely.  You can just type in what you want to know.  . . For example, I typed in \"4.3 inches in centimeters\": http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&lr=&q=4.3+feet+in+centimeters&btnG=Search", 
            "Click on the link below and the Conversion & Equivalents are listed on the page.  . . The second link that I provided gives you the sites for Metric to U.S. conversion, Farenheit and Celcius conversion, etc.", 
            "This website has just about any type of convertion you can think of."
        ], 
        "answer": "I recommend tables of conversion factors or units.  An example is one provided by Wikipedia for free.", 
        "id": "4382324"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "How should I encrypt/pw protect my backup files on an external harddrive for easy recovery on any machine?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "I recently backed up and restored a bunch of files using Roxio's Backup MyPC Deluxe, which was bundled with my copy of Easy Media Creator 7.5.  I don't know how secure the encryption is, but it definitely lets you recover files to any computer.  I would assume that any of the more recognized packages (i.e. Norton/Dantz Retrospect/Ghost) would let you restore files to a different machine as this seems to be a core feature of a backup program.", 
            "PGP is the grandaddy of all encryption software, and I think they have a home version for disk encryption: http://www.pgp.com/solutions/pgp_home_office.html"
        ], 
        "answer": "I recently backed up and restored a bunch of files using Roxio's Backup MyPC Deluxe, which was bundled with my copy of Easy Media Creator 7.5.  I don't know how secure the encryption is, but it definitely lets you recover files to any computer.  I would assume that any of the more recognized packages (i.e. Norton/Dantz Retrospect/Ghost) would let you restore files to a different machine as this seems to be a core feature of a backup program.", 
        "id": "1947336"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Health", 
        "question": "Why hasn't anyone found a cure for the common cold yet?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "There are 100's of strains of the virus that causes the common cold, and each one is constantly mutating, and so finding a cure is like a 100 moving targets, all going in a different direction.  But yes, maybe it is a conspiracy of the big drug companies, just like the CIA caused AIDS :)", 
            "The common cold is the highest form of evolution for any disease.  All diseases should aspire to be the common cold.  Most younger, stupider diseases haven't figured out yet that if you kill your host, or even make them really ugly, you won't spread any more.  I have deep respect for the cold. I had a 2-month loving relationship with a cold virus while I was in college once -- I was very satisfying: it was another living thing to keep me company at night with assorted wetness of mucous membranes, it was someone who would listen to me without judgment, and it gave me a reason to pamper myself.  Hey, when you're young and stupid, what more are you looking for in a relationship?  And now that I'm older and wiser, I use the common cold as a powerful indication: if I get a cold, that means that something was wrong enough in my life that my immune system succumbed to it, and tells me very clearly that I need to be taking beter care of myself.  Hooray for the Cold!"
        ], 
        "answer": "There are 100's of strains of the virus that causes the common cold, and each one is constantly mutating, and so finding a cure is like a 100 moving targets, all going in a different direction.  But yes, maybe it is a conspiracy of the big drug companies, just like the CIA caused AIDS :)", 
        "id": "4113055"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Social Science", 
        "question": "What is the difference between Askers and Answerers?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "one can argue that in order to become an answerer you first need to be an asker- how would you gather a more then common knowledge information- you need to inquire, thus ask many questions. only then you can answer other's people questions.. . So- He who wants to become an answerer must first be an asker", 
            "ego? No seriously, I try to imagine us all on a continuum of how much stuff we know. There are people higher than me and people lower than me on the path to knowing a lot of stuff. I get advice from the people higher than me on a given subject. A person that is lower than me in one subject is higher than me on another, so I am an asker and an answering. Forever! Always more to know!!", 
            "Can one truely ever be said to be an answerer? or an asker for that matter? in the manifested world there is to much to be learned in a lifetime? best to be equally be open to both teacher and student."
        ], 
        "answer": "one can argue that in order to become an answerer you first need to be an asker- how would you gather a more then common knowledge information- you need to inquire, thus ask many questions. only then you can answer other's people questions.. . So- He who wants to become an answerer must first be an asker", 
        "id": "4071191"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "Which Internet browser is the best and why?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "I am using Firefox, because it has tabbed browsing, tighter security, many useful extensions, and .. I like  the fox symbol.", 
            "Internet Explorer is still the best. C'mon guys. I think we are just favouring the underdog", 
            "Firefox here also....hate IE...it really sucks...tried Opera...liked Firefox better.", 
            "Same here about the Firefox. I used to have too many pop ups from hacking websites and since i got firefox i havent had any.", 
            "Wihout any doubts Firefox 1.5+", 
            "Internet Explorer has got the most functionality..... It is has 10x the features......  http://www.microsoft.com/windows/ie/evaluation/features/default.mspx. 10x the support... http://www.microsoft.com/windows/ie/community/default.mspx. It has tabbed browsing,too, by the way.... http://www.microsoft.com/windows/IE/community/columns/tabbedbrowsing.mspx. They say Firefox doesn't get spyware, but I had bad spyware last year and found the same group of websites added into my favorites on both browsers over and over, so that is just not true.", 
            "IE is always best and fast.", 
            "I'd say Firefox as it is open-source, conforms to standards, is available for all major platforms (Mac/Win/Linux) and has many customizations possible through add-ons."
        ], 
        "answer": "I am using Firefox, because it has tabbed browsing, tighter security, many useful extensions, and .. I like  the fox symbol.", 
        "id": "3658429"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "if i have 2 pc's that have a wireless connection how do i get both pcs 2 share information and share a printer", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Don't use the subnet 255.255.255.255.  This is a broadcast and won't work.  Use 255.255.255.0 as your subnet.", 
            "Give them IP address of same range then Just run the network setup  wizard for wirless", 
            "Make sure they are on the same subnet which you could put to 255.255.255.255 then an ip of say 192.168.2.2 then your next pc should be same sub net and ip of 192.168.2.3. then make sure they are on the same workgroup, named whatever you want like HOME. Then you have to enable sharing on the computer where the printer is connected to.", 
            "When they both have wireless installed on them, just make a home network as you do it in thenormal way(cable) then you can share your data.", 
            "I actually didn't deal with wireless networks b4. but in the control panel u will find a \"Wireless Network Setup Wizard\". It is a wizard that should manage to configure it for u. . I'm assuming u have Windows Xp SP2"
        ], 
        "answer": "I actually didn't deal with wireless networks b4. but in the control panel u will find a \"Wireless Network Setup Wizard\". It is a wizard that should manage to configure it for u. . I'm assuming u have Windows Xp SP2", 
        "id": "1282724"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "I have 2 40 gig hard drives,win98se,and I want to get a new drive say 160 or more,how do I get the info switch", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "It appears that the question period has expired. If you have received an answer that meets your needs, please choose a 'best answer.'. Regards.", 
            "Yes, 98SE cant handle large hard drives.  Windows XP can.  However, Windows 98SE has the Fat32 file system and Windows XP formats the hard drive in NTFS.  First disconnect the 40 GB hard drives.  Probably, if XP allows you to format the new 160 GB hard-drive in Fat32 file format, then do so and install XP on the 160 GB hard-drive.  Reconnect the old drives one by one (while keeping the new hard drive).  Windows XP will recognize the old drives if all 3 drives are in the Fat32 format.  Then you can simply drag and drop files from the old drives to the new drive."
        ], 
        "answer": "It appears that the question period has expired. If you have received an answer that meets your needs, please choose a 'best answer.'. Regards.", 
        "id": "99357"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Health", 
        "question": "How do you use dental floss?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "I agree with the previous two answers...go see a dentist/hygienist, get a professional cleaning, and ask for instruction on how to floss correctly.  It may help prevent gum disease, and allow you to keep your teeth for a lifetime!  (which is how long healthy teeth last!)", 
            "See a dentist every 6 months", 
            "I'd go in for a check-up as soon as possible. Your dentist will be able to tell you how to best care for your teeth."
        ], 
        "answer": "I agree with the previous two answers...go see a dentist/hygienist, get a professional cleaning, and ask for instruction on how to floss correctly.  It may help prevent gum disease, and allow you to keep your teeth for a lifetime!  (which is how long healthy teeth last!)", 
        "id": "563604"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "How do you save online movies for play later?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "what do you mean by save movies? where are you getting them from", 
            "I'm wondering this too. E-mail me if you find out. Thanks"
        ], 
        "answer": "what do you mean by save movies? where are you getting them from", 
        "id": "225961"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Pets", 
        "question": "HOW CAN I GET A JOB?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "First - education helps. Second, experience. Third, and some would argue most importantly, knowing people who are in positions to get you a job.", 
            "Well, first you have to pound the concrete not every place advertise in the newspapers. It is a good place to start but when you run out of openings there. Try the online job search sights... monster.com, yahoo jobs. Send your resume out... put an application at your favorite stores ect. And make sure you look nice when you are applying for these jobs. But the most important hint I can give you is call back, call and email the places that you have applied at. I usually do it every other day until they tell me that they have already filled the position or until I get an interview. Remember looking for a job is a full time job in its self"
        ], 
        "answer": "First - education helps. Second, experience. Third, and some would argue most importantly, knowing people who are in positions to get you a job.", 
        "id": "1419878"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "how do I stop pop ups from Best Offers?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Stop using IE and get Firefox 1.5 with the google toolbar.  That will nix most pop ups altogether. Or use Google toolbar with IE and enable the pop-up blocker.", 
            "Or if Best offers is installed on your computer as a result of installing another program, you have to uninstall that program to uninstall Best Offers. I had the same problem when I downloaded Kaaza, a **** load of programs was also installed. The only way to uninstall the other programs was to Uninstall Kaaza first.", 
            "It appears that the question period has expired. If you have received an answer that meets your needs, please choose a 'best answer.'. Regards."
        ], 
        "answer": "Stop using IE and get Firefox 1.5 with the google toolbar.  That will nix most pop ups altogether. Or use Google toolbar with IE and enable the pop-up blocker.", 
        "id": "1100745"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "News & Events", 
        "question": "Why is there terrorism?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "A simple answer is hate.  By nature we hate things for various reasons, so terrorism is just acts of strong hate.", 
            "intolerence hate and envy are polution to the human soul.if left to fester without hope, education, maybe a productive life theres no feeling of self worth so why is anyone elses life so important.there will always be good vs. evil.", 
            "because capitialism work only too well, the world becomes divided from the haves and have nots.. . terrorism seems to get our attention, so it works to an extent.  americans were the terrorist to the british back in 1776 thru 1783", 
            "Perhaps because injustice on a large scale (such as the Israeli occupation of Palestine) can cause people to feel extremely angry, utterly powerless, and as if they have nothing to lose. People in this situation may believe that the only way to be heard, and to change their situation, is through violence. This is terribly sad.", 
            "This country has been terrorizing the world ever since the Native Americans defeat. Among the countries that have been terrorized by the USA after WWII are: Panama, Guatemala, El Salvador, Granada, Colombia, Iran, Iraq, etc.. Or are you talking about the people unable to take it anymore, opt to retaliate in a small way these atrocities.", 
            "Because Bill Clinton couldn't get away from Monica long enough to make a rational decision"
        ], 
        "answer": "A simple answer is hate.  By nature we hate things for various reasons, so terrorism is just acts of strong hate.", 
        "id": "165751"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Yahoo! Products", 
        "question": "I am not able to run my messenger from my desktop so i need to know why and what si the problum?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "\"not able to run\" ??   What happens when you click the shortcut - absolutely nothing, OR does it appear to start to open, then vanish almost immediately (OR something quite different) ??", 
            "you have to down load it on ur desktop if you have then you will be able to use it"
        ], 
        "answer": "\"not able to run\" ??   What happens when you click the shortcut - absolutely nothing, OR does it appear to start to open, then vanish almost immediately (OR something quite different) ??", 
        "id": "4296727"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Science & Mathematics", 
        "question": "why do clouds turn dark when its about to rain?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "A cloud compsition is primarlly just billions of drops of water or ice.  When such a cloud formation has an influx of water/ice, ie it's mass increases to include more water/ice, light finds it hard to pass through the mass, thus making it darker for us to see.. . In a normal cloud, light can pass through the water/ice within the cloud and we see it as a distorted white/bluish/greyish/greenish hue.  But when the cloud is too thick with water/ice, the light doesn't pass through so easily and we see a darker spectrum.", 
            "because they are full of moisture (future rain) and therefore do not transmit light like a cloud with less moisture content"
        ], 
        "answer": "A cloud compsition is primarlly just billions of drops of water or ice.  When such a cloud formation has an influx of water/ice, ie it's mass increases to include more water/ice, light finds it hard to pass through the mass, thus making it darker for us to see.. . In a normal cloud, light can pass through the water/ice within the cloud and we see it as a distorted white/bluish/greyish/greenish hue.  But when the cloud is too thick with water/ice, the light doesn't pass through so easily and we see a darker spectrum.", 
        "id": "1366560"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Consumer Electronics", 
        "question": "Why isn't calicum carbide used in fuel cells?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "There are other solid propellants that are more stable and efficient e.g. ammonium perchlorate NH4ClO4. Chemically speaking, calcium carbide is commonly used when welding metal in the form of acetylene...its tank technically being a \"fuel cell.\"", 
            "Here is a better question, why would it be?"
        ], 
        "answer": "There are other solid propellants that are more stable and efficient e.g. ammonium perchlorate NH4ClO4. Chemically speaking, calcium carbide is commonly used when welding metal in the form of acetylene...its tank technically being a \"fuel cell.\"", 
        "id": "688117"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Science & Mathematics", 
        "question": "what is the answer to: P=2L + 2w for w ?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "That depends on what L and P are.  If you plug the permitter and length in, you can get width W.. . If you want a formula that will yield W, it's: (P-2L)/2 = W", 
            "perimeter of a rectangle with length L and width w is =2L+2w", 
            "P/2-L,depends upon the value of P & L"
        ], 
        "answer": "That depends on what L and P are.  If you plug the permitter and length in, you can get width W.. . If you want a formula that will yield W, it's: (P-2L)/2 = W", 
        "id": "4274366"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "how to become a perfect hardware engineer as i am undergoing btech in CSE in second year?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Learn well the fundamentals of Computer Science.  Hardware may constantly change (Moore's Law) but the underlying theories will last forever.  Good luck.", 
            "Do Microsoft certifiction or Cisco course. Do lot of practical work on PC's."
        ], 
        "answer": "Learn well the fundamentals of Computer Science.  Hardware may constantly change (Moore's Law) but the underlying theories will last forever.  Good luck.", 
        "id": "4254170"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Food & Drink", 
        "question": "why chicory is added to coffee?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "It was originally added as a way to 'stretch' the coffee,which was very expensive. Eventually people became accustomed to the taste and began to prefer it. It is now added as a flavoring. It is most often associated with the city of New Orleans and beignets.", 
            "or else it would be bitter"
        ], 
        "answer": "It was originally added as a way to 'stretch' the coffee,which was very expensive. Eventually people became accustomed to the taste and began to prefer it. It is now added as a flavoring. It is most often associated with the city of New Orleans and beignets.", 
        "id": "3174498"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Politics & Government", 
        "question": "How do you vote in Iraq?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "citizens are went to election centers and select the prefered list of candidate . electronic election is not used", 
            "you vote and dip you finger in green ink so you cant vate again"
        ], 
        "answer": "citizens are went to election centers and select the prefered list of candidate . electronic election is not used", 
        "id": "1105782"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Business & Finance", 
        "question": "what does a 4'x8'- 1/2\" sheet of drywall weigh...one sheet, not the double?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Just a guestimate but I've handeled 100's. I'd say 65 lbs.", 
            "according to a repair article on the popular mechanics site..... a regular sheet of 1/2\" weighs a bit more than 54 lbs.  i know that green board (moisture resistant) is heavier."
        ], 
        "answer": "according to a repair article on the popular mechanics site..... a regular sheet of 1/2\" weighs a bit more than 54 lbs.  i know that green board (moisture resistant) is heavier.", 
        "id": "2095228"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Consumer Electronics", 
        "question": "what is meant by protocol?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "A protocol would be a standard procedure or practice that is in place...usually in a work place but can apply to alot of things. It just basically says if this happens then we should do...steps 1 2 and 3.", 
            "Protocol is a precise and detailed plan of action."
        ], 
        "answer": "A protocol would be a standard procedure or practice that is in place...usually in a work place but can apply to alot of things. It just basically says if this happens then we should do...steps 1 2 and 3.", 
        "id": "3818889"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "How to convert a pdf document to word document without losing the formatting?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "For PDF to Word conversion, I've found that SolidPDF does a good job.  It does a very good job of preserving formatting - not perfect, but very good.", 
            "You Can Use some Conferting Software like Abboy. \"Pdf Transformer\""
        ], 
        "answer": "For PDF to Word conversion, I've found that SolidPDF does a good job.  It does a very good job of preserving formatting - not perfect, but very good.", 
        "id": "4131499"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Cars & Transportation", 
        "question": "How can I as a teenager reduce my car insurance premiums?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "good student discount. Some give discounts for safety courses.", 
            "Get on your parents insurance policy.", 
            "the only discount that you yourself can get is good student. other than that you are a high risk category especially if you are male. yep sex discrimination in action. gotta love statistics.", 
            "The main thing you can do is to have completed a valid and state certified driver education course, since that will lower your premiums.  Also of course you must keep a very clean record - no tickets or violations. As time goes on the premiums will automaticaly go down each year if you keep a clean record."
        ], 
        "answer": "good student discount. Some give discounts for safety courses.", 
        "id": "3593337"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Business & Finance", 
        "question": "Do you believe in reincarnation?And why?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Yes.. It is not a thing I believe, it is a thing I experienced, it is about seeing.", 
            "No...because I have never been reincarnated."
        ], 
        "answer": "Yes.. It is not a thing I believe, it is a thing I experienced, it is about seeing.", 
        "id": "3484454"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Food & Drink", 
        "question": "what is a \"fruit baller\"?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "scoop-like utinsil that is used to scoop the meat of fruit in ball shapes.. . See link below for an image.", 
            "It's used for scooping little balls out of fruit such as melons or pears.  It also called a Melon Baller.. . My link below has a picture of one.", 
            "Cut a cucumber in small pieces, use the fruit baller to make a whole (don't get the other end open please) and make little cups. Fill them up with some wasabi and salmon roe, and you got a beautiful and delicious hors d'ouvre."
        ], 
        "answer": "scoop-like utinsil that is used to scoop the meat of fruit in ball shapes.. . See link below for an image.", 
        "id": "3942631"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "how i eraise the old words in my search bar?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "On Yahoo toolbar search, the pencil click it and click clear recent searches.", 
            "tools, internet options, clear history, delete cookies, delete files, then go to the content tab, click autocomplete and uncheck the boxes there.. . and while you have the internet options open you can go back to the first tab and click clear history, delete cookies and delete temporary files."
        ], 
        "answer": "tools, internet options, clear history, delete cookies, delete files, then go to the content tab, click autocomplete and uncheck the boxes there.. . and while you have the internet options open you can go back to the first tab and click clear history, delete cookies and delete temporary files.", 
        "id": "2816925"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Health", 
        "question": "Why do babies have to come out head first?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "As the skull bones are flexible at this point it is easier for a baby to be born this way, even though they can be born vaginally in other positions.", 
            "if the baby comes out feet first, I runs the risk of have the cord wrapped around the neck,and can choke it to death. If the baby comes out head first, doctor can make sure the cord is not wrapped around the neck. Also the head and shoulders need to come out first as to allow the vagina to stretch enough to allow them to slide out.", 
            "because if they come out legs first, their hands would be caught and it would complicate the pregnancy.  there are cases where the baby comes out legs first, and they would further assist the passage.  But, alot of people opt to have a c section if that were the case, because alot of times, they would know before hand when this is about to happen.", 
            "I don't know, but I do know it would be more painful if they came out feet first, and kicking!!"
        ], 
        "answer": "if the baby comes out feet first, I runs the risk of have the cord wrapped around the neck,and can choke it to death. If the baby comes out head first, doctor can make sure the cord is not wrapped around the neck. Also the head and shoulders need to come out first as to allow the vagina to stretch enough to allow them to slide out.", 
        "id": "2722698"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Business & Finance", 
        "question": "how is a digital camera work ?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Most of the camera works exactly the same as any other... there's a lens that focuses and a shutter that is normally closed, blocking light from passing through the camera, but opens when you want to take a picture. In a film camera, the light that gets through the shutter while it is open hits film, which is chemically sensitive to light. Digital cameras use a charged-couple device instead. This is a photosensitive (sensitive to light) computer chip, which converts the light energy into information that can be read by a computer.", 
            "Here's a detailed article which answers your question.", 
            "Digital photography, as opposed to film photography, uses an electronic sensor to record the image as binary data."
        ], 
        "answer": "Most of the camera works exactly the same as any other... there's a lens that focuses and a shutter that is normally closed, blocking light from passing through the camera, but opens when you want to take a picture. In a film camera, the light that gets through the shutter while it is open hits film, which is chemically sensitive to light. Digital cameras use a charged-couple device instead. This is a photosensitive (sensitive to light) computer chip, which converts the light energy into information that can be read by a computer.", 
        "id": "3384343"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "How do I access my Yahoo mail settings?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Login in to yahoo mail. Top right you'll see OPTIONS.", 
            "I don't know anything about your problem with attachments but when you first go to your mail on the left side of the screen, near the top, there are four links: what's new, mail for mobile, upgrades & OPTIONS.  click that.", 
            "After you log in to your account, click on the \"Options\" link on the main page in the upper righthand corner. From there, you will find links to all of your Yahoo Mail settings.", 
            "after signing in see the Option link in top right corner of the page."
        ], 
        "answer": "After you log in to your account, click on the \"Options\" link on the main page in the upper righthand corner. From there, you will find links to all of your Yahoo Mail settings.", 
        "id": "292048"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Games & Recreation", 
        "question": "how can you connect ur ps2 to ur computer?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "usb cable", 
            "usinng a USB 2.0 cable to connect a PSP to a computer wont work. There are computers that come with the 3 plugs(red,yellow,white). If your computer does not have that, there are special decices that do that. Not plain cables, and they can cost a lot."
        ], 
        "answer": "usinng a USB 2.0 cable to connect a PSP to a computer wont work. There are computers that come with the 3 plugs(red,yellow,white). If your computer does not have that, there are special decices that do that. Not plain cables, and they can cost a lot.", 
        "id": "1873488"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Society & Culture", 
        "question": "WHy is my son gay?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Your son was made truly special by God. It can be difficult for you acceptin that he is homosexual, but remember that he needs to feel that you still love him, because of whom he is, his sexual orientations, doesnt change the bone that connects you both. If you are having problems acceptin his homosexuality it would be good if you talk with an specialist (psychologist) or join a group of parents with gay children. Any of them could help you come closer and understand more the feelings of your son.", 
            "when a kid comes in to the world, you say if you want hem your dont, so when the kid comein you take hem as he is, and yes we are all born gay or st8. that is what i belive, and  it can run in your fam too.", 
            "I'm not gay, but you should except him for who he is. Maybe he's experimenting with the sexes. But if you don't like the fact that he's gay,maybe dicipline would help,maybe."
        ], 
        "answer": "Your son was made truly special by God. It can be difficult for you acceptin that he is homosexual, but remember that he needs to feel that you still love him, because of whom he is, his sexual orientations, doesnt change the bone that connects you both. If you are having problems acceptin his homosexuality it would be good if you talk with an specialist (psychologist) or join a group of parents with gay children. Any of them could help you come closer and understand more the feelings of your son.", 
        "id": "2490401"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Business & Finance", 
        "question": "how is the job market for ophthalmologists in washington state?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Lots of work, but don't count on lot's of clients, as you know, jobs are going over seas, leaving only retail and service workers in the state, who have no insurance, therefore, cannot afford your services. isnt trickle down economics great!!!!!!!!!!", 
            "I think he meant that many people cannot afford to go to an eye doctor because they are not being paid as much.  Therefore, if people cannot afford to go to an opthamologist, he will not have much business.", 
            "I can't answer this question exactly. However, the guy above obviously does not know what an opthalmoligst really is, its not like you can go to one over seas ;)"
        ], 
        "answer": "Lots of work, but don't count on lot's of clients, as you know, jobs are going over seas, leaving only retail and service workers in the state, who have no insurance, therefore, cannot afford your services. isnt trickle down economics great!!!!!!!!!!", 
        "id": "2083534"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Business & Finance", 
        "question": "Why is it that dogs whine?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Sounds like the dog is poorly trained.  If it's anything like my dog, it wants to come inside to be with people, but when it gets near people it can't control its excitement.  My dog also whines because she wants a cookie.  Next time you go over, bring the dog a giant chew bone, something that will keep it busy for hours.", 
            "probably because it doesn't like the balcony. dogs like big open spaces to roam around not to be trapped in a cage on a balcony somewhere.", 
            "Maybe because it has trouble digesting the cheese served with that whine.", 
            "maybe becuase the dog wants something and your realtives won't give it to them. so he/she will whine and whine until he/she gets it.", 
            "I don't own a dog & I am terribly scared of them. Although, from my observation, I think dogs are like babies. They need a lot of attention from the owner.. . I am guessing this dog might be looking for the owner's attention or is just lonely."
        ], 
        "answer": "Sounds like the dog is poorly trained.  If it's anything like my dog, it wants to come inside to be with people, but when it gets near people it can't control its excitement.  My dog also whines because she wants a cookie.  Next time you go over, bring the dog a giant chew bone, something that will keep it busy for hours.", 
        "id": "2512410"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "how can you tell if someone has opened your email?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "This is not something you can see with Yahoo mail.  Both the sender and receiver must have an e-mail program (such as Outlook) to utilize return receipt.", 
            "If the person has read the email from the Yahoo website itself, there is no way of knowing unless he/she replies you.  If he/she is using an email client such as outlook, then you can probably ask for email receipt confirmation."
        ], 
        "answer": "This is not something you can see with Yahoo mail.  Both the sender and receiver must have an e-mail program (such as Outlook) to utilize return receipt.", 
        "id": "1159613"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Politics & Government", 
        "question": "What are the chances that Israel launches an attack to prevent Iranian nuclear ambitions?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Israel will launch an attack on Iran only if it feels that it is the only way to prevent an attack. I could see Israel bombing a vehicle that was to supply enriched Uranium if they felt that bombing this vehicle would delay Iran's Nuclear plans by some significant aount of time.. . Note that when Israel launched an attack in Iraq's Nuclear plant (condemned by the world at the time) they made sure to do so when they knew there would be minimal casualties on the ground.", 
            "1. Iran didn't threaten Israel, the Iranian president said it should be wiped off map, and it doesn't mean anything, and is just a slogan.. 2. Israel won't dare attacking Iran, cause it knows how much military power iran has. If the war happens it would be some thing like the war between Iraq and Iran. All the western and Arabic countries supported Iraq, but Iran relied on it's people and won the war, even though it ended with a peace agreement, every one knows the winner of that war was Iran.. 3. Western countries won't let Israel attack Iran. Iran is one of the world's biggest suppliers of oil. The price of oil is currently about 60 dollars, with a war the price is going to be about 80-90 dollars, and it would cause unrecoverable damages to the economy of western countries.. 4. Iran is much larger than Israel and has a bigger and stronger army. The power of the armies of both countries almost matches up in air force, and navy. But iran has a much stronger Army. Israel is small so if Iran target Israel with missle, Israel will experience unrecoverable damages. But Israel can't target Iran with missles, and if it does it can't make that much of a damage.( Note the new anti missle and aircraft systems Iran bought from Russia, which covers the entire western parts of Iran.) . 5. There are alot of american forces around Iran that if Israel attacks and U.S. supports it, Iran can easily hit them. . 6. Iran has alot of allies around Israel. Syria, Lebanon, and even Palestine.. 7. People of Iran fully support it in war, even if they hate their government, the spirit of Iranians is that they won't let any foreign person or country rule over them, and as they did in the war between Iran and Iraq they will fully support their country in the war.. 8. God is with Iranians. Iranians have a strong faith in god, and with that faith they can do anything."
        ], 
        "answer": "Israel will launch an attack on Iran only if it feels that it is the only way to prevent an attack. I could see Israel bombing a vehicle that was to supply enriched Uranium if they felt that bombing this vehicle would delay Iran's Nuclear plans by some significant aount of time.. . Note that when Israel launched an attack in Iraq's Nuclear plant (condemned by the world at the time) they made sure to do so when they knew there would be minimal casualties on the ground.", 
        "id": "358866"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Business & Finance", 
        "question": "Why are gold prices going up?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "1 The cost to mine it is getting more expensive.(FUEL & Labor and repair parts.2 The value of a dollar versus other curency is lower(compared to some other Countrys currancy rate).3 Gold is being bought as investments.So gold will hold more of its value compared to a dollar.", 
            "Coz the mines are being depleted & gold is not in transancted in market."
        ], 
        "answer": "1 The cost to mine it is getting more expensive.(FUEL & Labor and repair parts.2 The value of a dollar versus other curency is lower(compared to some other Countrys currancy rate).3 Gold is being bought as investments.So gold will hold more of its value compared to a dollar.", 
        "id": "1434390"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Business & Finance", 
        "question": "How can I make free - full free- International calls ( from and to countries out of USA)?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "The best way would to find a free voice chat service which allows pc to pc calls rather than trying to find a free phone service.  A simple search will give you a multitude of providers to pick from.", 
            "www.skype.com", 
            "Bright house!", 
            "you can go and apply for the verizon freedom package were you can make call out of the country free from yor home", 
            "If both parties have the internet then MSN messenger has a Voice Chat function, as do many Instant Message programs. If you are not a fan of IM's, try Ventrillo or Teamspeak.. . Skype has already been mentioned.. . You can purchase telephone handsets for your PC if a headset/mic combo is not suitable."
        ], 
        "answer": "If both parties have the internet then MSN messenger has a Voice Chat function, as do many Instant Message programs. If you are not a fan of IM's, try Ventrillo or Teamspeak.. . Skype has already been mentioned.. . You can purchase telephone handsets for your PC if a headset/mic combo is not suitable.", 
        "id": "1661895"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "What is the difference between Blog and Podcast ?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Well Blog is read. And Podcast is listened. Blog files are html (or php/asp/other web language-generated HTML) files. Meanwhile Podcast files are mp3s, which you can download to your iPod or other mp3 players.", 
            "A podcast is an audio weblog. Instead of publishing just text and pictures, podcasters publish mp3 files, that can then be downloaded in a mp3 player, or played directly from the site.", 
            "Blog comes from the words weB LOG, a web based diary . . Podcast from iPOD broadCAST, an audio version of a blog, normally an audio file that can be subscribed to, a podcast reader will download and play it for you."
        ], 
        "answer": "Well Blog is read. And Podcast is listened. Blog files are html (or php/asp/other web language-generated HTML) files. Meanwhile Podcast files are mp3s, which you can download to your iPod or other mp3 players.", 
        "id": "3319666"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "how do you intergrate ssl with a web based site?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Integrating SSL layer with IIS is just installing the security software from  the vendor and installing the digital certificate. You need to open the port 483 also to enable the HTTPs connection.", 
            "You will need to get a ssl certificate and then implement it on the web server.  In the source section are detailed guidelines from Thawte (one of the leaders in SSL Certifiates)."
        ], 
        "answer": "Integrating SSL layer with IIS is just installing the security software from  the vendor and installing the digital certificate. You need to open the port 483 also to enable the HTTPs connection.", 
        "id": "1300873"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "Why is the <link /> element the unsung hero of (X)HTML?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "I don't know if I'd call it a \"hero\", but it is a useful way to provide metadata for a site in a way that browsers can understand.  For example, Slashdot uses it to link to authors of articles, parents of articles, yesterday's news, etc.. . Unfortunately, most browsers don't do anything with most <link/> elements (with the exception of stylesheets), so we'll have to wait and see what people really do with them when people can use them.", 
            "This is a well documented answer, we should select it and close out this question since it could be valuable material to others."
        ], 
        "answer": "I don't know if I'd call it a \"hero\", but it is a useful way to provide metadata for a site in a way that browsers can understand.  For example, Slashdot uses it to link to authors of articles, parents of articles, yesterday's news, etc.. . Unfortunately, most browsers don't do anything with most <link/> elements (with the exception of stylesheets), so we'll have to wait and see what people really do with them when people can use them.", 
        "id": "1445703"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Society & Culture", 
        "question": "Why do people steal the baby jesus at christmas?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Those who do this have no respect for other's religion or personal property. It's just the world we live in...sad to say.", 
            "It's usually just a prank.  Many people think nativity scenes are rather tacky, and others just want to get a rise out of people.  There are certainly some very uptight religious types who would be shocked and horrified by such activity all out of proportion to it's real seriousness.", 
            "its called being a moron like you.", 
            "Maybe because they're sick, sociopathic, anti-religious pedophiles!", 
            "maybe they are attracted to him being a baby, or maybe they are just stupid and don't care about the feelings and property of others..", 
            "Anything that isn't unmoveable is subject to petty theft.  It's just an everyday prank and it's not the real baby Jesus anyway, just a prop.", 
            "because it's funny"
        ], 
        "answer": "Those who do this have no respect for other's religion or personal property. It's just the world we live in...sad to say.", 
        "id": "210136"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Arts & Humanities", 
        "question": "Do you think Draco Malfoy will turn to the order of the Pheonix?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "that would be a really neat twist to things but i think his fear will win in the end.  draco fears voldemort more than he listens to his conscience.", 
            "I keep getting the feeling that he will. I know I want him to (the less bad guys the better). I think he might, but you never know what J.K. will do."
        ], 
        "answer": "that would be a really neat twist to things but i think his fear will win in the end.  draco fears voldemort more than he listens to his conscience.", 
        "id": "3664866"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Science & Mathematics", 
        "question": "how is the climate in chennai city?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "right now in chennai its pouring!! with an extreme monsoon this season with almost 3 cyclones hitting the costal city, the city is drenched :)", 
            "Warm all year round. See the sources for a link. . . \"The weather is pleasant in December with temperature hovering in the range of 22-26 degree celcius and humidity in the order 40-60%.\". http://www.cs.iitm.ernet.in/~ac05/chennai.html. . \"Chennai can be extremely hot and humid, but does benefit from cooling sea breezes in the late afternoons and evenings.\". http://internal.10best.com/Chennai/locationDetails.html"
        ], 
        "answer": "right now in chennai its pouring!! with an extreme monsoon this season with almost 3 cyclones hitting the costal city, the city is drenched :)", 
        "id": "4306548"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Business & Finance", 
        "question": "how to apply for a credit card through Lebanon's super wal-mart?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Go to the Gift Registry Kiosk by the Jewelry Department. A Jewelry Associate can assist you if you need help. If you are approved, you will get a shopping pass that you can use that day.", 
            "Go to the service desk and ask."
        ], 
        "answer": "Go to the Gift Registry Kiosk by the Jewelry Department. A Jewelry Associate can assist you if you need help. If you are approved, you will get a shopping pass that you can use that day.", 
        "id": "2495389"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Yahoo! Products", 
        "question": "how do u transfer mail that have been received from an account to another account?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "you may forward it manually to the other account. For some, there'll be an option to forward all incoming mails to a different address. If you're using the free yahoo account, you wont get this option.", 
            "email it to the other account?"
        ], 
        "answer": "you may forward it manually to the other account. For some, there'll be an option to forward all incoming mails to a different address. If you're using the free yahoo account, you wont get this option.", 
        "id": "2552591"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Consumer Electronics", 
        "question": "HOW DO I CRASH MY LOST NOKIA 7610 USING IMEI ?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "complain to police... they will find it for u... better than crash!!", 
            "depending on the service provider offer, some companies offer the service of locking your stolen phone by preventing the specific (IMEI; International Mobile Equipment Idendity) from accessing the network. they have (EIR) Equipment idendity register they just have to delet that your IMEI number from the database register, but also i have to tell that there are many programs used now to unlock those closed phones. in addation there must be some integration between the Police and all mobile companies to have a complete shared database for the stolen phones. in that case the phone will not be used inside the whole country also it can be traced to catch the stealer."
        ], 
        "answer": "depending on the service provider offer, some companies offer the service of locking your stolen phone by preventing the specific (IMEI; International Mobile Equipment Idendity) from accessing the network. they have (EIR) Equipment idendity register they just have to delet that your IMEI number from the database register, but also i have to tell that there are many programs used now to unlock those closed phones. in addation there must be some integration between the Police and all mobile companies to have a complete shared database for the stolen phones. in that case the phone will not be used inside the whole country also it can be traced to catch the stealer.", 
        "id": "2434634"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Society & Culture", 
        "question": "what does the french word langap mean?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "perhaps you mean lagniappe?  if so it means a small bonus or gift...", 
            "Nothing, it's not a french word :)"
        ], 
        "answer": "perhaps you mean lagniappe?  if so it means a small bonus or gift...", 
        "id": "2124806"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Consumer Electronics", 
        "question": "my apple ipod 30 gig just locked up when i pluged it in why?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Um, maybe it's not formatted to windows or mac whichever comp you have.", 
            "did you try the soft reset or the hard reset? the hard reset might restore the factory settings, which MIGHT unlock your ipod. i'm not even sure theres a way to reset an ipod, now that i think about it. did you contact Apple?"
        ], 
        "answer": "did you try the soft reset or the hard reset? the hard reset might restore the factory settings, which MIGHT unlock your ipod. i'm not even sure theres a way to reset an ipod, now that i think about it. did you contact Apple?", 
        "id": "1603485"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Food & Drink", 
        "question": "what is the difference between ketchup and sauce?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Sauce is a very generic term referring to any semi-liquid condiment that is used to add flavor to food.. . Ketchup (or catsup) is a specific type of sauce that consists of tomato puree, vinegar, sweetener and spices, with the tomato being the dominant flavor.", 
            "Ketchup is a Brand Name i think, and it's made with tomato. Sauce is sauce..from any other products including tomato."
        ], 
        "answer": "Sauce is a very generic term referring to any semi-liquid condiment that is used to add flavor to food.. . Ketchup (or catsup) is a specific type of sauce that consists of tomato puree, vinegar, sweetener and spices, with the tomato being the dominant flavor.", 
        "id": "150664"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Yahoo! Products", 
        "question": "How do I make it so I am invisible when playing games?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "the only way 2 make yourself invisible is to use your stealth settings. to do so, just click on your status message and choose invisible to everyone. wen your done, just go back 2 being available", 
            "I'm not sure you can if you are playing in yahoo games with multiplayer but single player just do what the last guy said."
        ], 
        "answer": "the only way 2 make yourself invisible is to use your stealth settings. to do so, just click on your status message and choose invisible to everyone. wen your done, just go back 2 being available", 
        "id": "3052881"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Education & Reference", 
        "question": "what is the difference between perfume and cologne?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Want an answer a bit more technical?. . Perfume has 15% to 30% of perfume oils.. Eau de cologne has 3% to 5% of perfume oils.. In between are eau de toilette (4-8), and eau de parfum (15-18).", 
            "perfume is for girls, and cologne is for guys", 
            "most perfume is made from essential oils and cologne has alchol in it that dries out the skin. check the ingreadiant label as well as the label for lotions vs. body mooses and cremes.", 
            "Basically perfume is for girls and colgne is for guys. Perfume has more oils than cologne if you mean it that way"
        ], 
        "answer": "Want an answer a bit more technical?. . Perfume has 15% to 30% of perfume oils.. Eau de cologne has 3% to 5% of perfume oils.. In between are eau de toilette (4-8), and eau de parfum (15-18).", 
        "id": "114106"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "Why do we have social security numbers?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "When Social Security was started in the 1940's, it became to unweildy to try to administer it based upon the recipient's name (lots of John Smith's in the U.S.A.).  As such, a 9-digit number system was developed.  Numbers are assigned according to geographic birth location, and date.  Since it was a national system, and just about every citizen was required to have an SSN, it grew to be used as a national tracking system by both government and commercial entities.", 
            "i think it's so the goverment can keep it's people filed. i guess it's like a record tab. dunno."
        ], 
        "answer": "When Social Security was started in the 1940's, it became to unweildy to try to administer it based upon the recipient's name (lots of John Smith's in the U.S.A.).  As such, a 9-digit number system was developed.  Numbers are assigned according to geographic birth location, and date.  Since it was a national system, and just about every citizen was required to have an SSN, it grew to be used as a national tracking system by both government and commercial entities.", 
        "id": "837036"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "what is networking?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "To connect one PC other..U can easy to transfer data one pc to another pc.In N/W there are 3 types . # LAN(Local Area Network) Communications network that serves users within a confined geographical area. It is made up of servers, workstations, a network operating system and a communications link.. 2)# MAN(Metropolitan Area Network) Communications network that covers a geographic area such as a city or suburb.. 3)WAN(Wide Area Network) Communications network that covers wide geographic areas, such as states and countries.", 
            "What would you like to know about networking?", 
            "is a net that is working"
        ], 
        "answer": "To connect one PC other..U can easy to transfer data one pc to another pc.In N/W there are 3 types . # LAN(Local Area Network) Communications network that serves users within a confined geographical area. It is made up of servers, workstations, a network operating system and a communications link.. 2)# MAN(Metropolitan Area Network) Communications network that covers a geographic area such as a city or suburb.. 3)WAN(Wide Area Network) Communications network that covers wide geographic areas, such as states and countries.", 
        "id": "3103319"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Pets", 
        "question": "Why is my Dove making weird noises?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "What kind of \"weird noises\" is your dove making? It's impossible to answer this question without more information.", 
            "Maybe it's because you just left me standing. alone in a world that's so cold.... . Ask Prince.  :-)"
        ], 
        "answer": "What kind of \"weird noises\" is your dove making? It's impossible to answer this question without more information.", 
        "id": "746854"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "what is trillian and what is the web address?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Trillian is a fully featured, stand-alone, skinnable chat client that supports AIM, ICQ, MSN, Yahoo Messenger, and IRC. It provides capabilities not possible with original network clients, while supporting standard features such as audio chat, file transfers, group chats, chat rooms, buddy icons, multiple simultaneous connections to the same network, server-side contact importing, typing notification, direct connection (AIM), proxy support, encrypted messaging (AIM/ICQ), SMS support, and privacy settings.", 
            "Trillian is a multi-network Instant Messaging client. It connects to various Supported Mediums allowing you to communicate with people on different messaging systems."
        ], 
        "answer": "Trillian is a fully featured, stand-alone, skinnable chat client that supports AIM, ICQ, MSN, Yahoo Messenger, and IRC. It provides capabilities not possible with original network clients, while supporting standard features such as audio chat, file transfers, group chats, chat rooms, buddy icons, multiple simultaneous connections to the same network, server-side contact importing, typing notification, direct connection (AIM), proxy support, encrypted messaging (AIM/ICQ), SMS support, and privacy settings.", 
        "id": "1706139"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Society & Culture", 
        "question": "Why do people still make secret admirer letters?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "I think sometimes it's hard to express our feelings openly, but we feel more comfortable expressing them in a note or letter.  Sometimes I prefer to write a letter because it gives me time to think about exactly what I want to say.  Also, it's fun when you know who wrote the letter and they don't!", 
            "If you received one, you probably deserved it. Wasn't it nice?", 
            "Oh, it's the romance of it.  I think they are great."
        ], 
        "answer": "I think sometimes it's hard to express our feelings openly, but we feel more comfortable expressing them in a note or letter.  Sometimes I prefer to write a letter because it gives me time to think about exactly what I want to say.  Also, it's fun when you know who wrote the letter and they don't!", 
        "id": "2799240"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Business & Finance", 
        "question": "what is internet?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "\"The Internet, or simply the Net (and often erroneously synonymous with World Wide Web), is the publicly accessible worldwide system of interconnected computer networks that transmit data by packet switching using a standardized Internet Protocol (IP) and many other protocols. It is made up of thousands of smaller commercial, academic, domestic and government networks. It carries various information and services, such as electronic mail, online chat, and the interlinked web pages and other documents of the World Wide Web.\"", 
            "Someone PLEASE HELP US. S.O.S. LOL", 
            "The Internet, or simply the Net (and often erroneously synonymous with World Wide Web), is the publicly accessible worldwide system of interconnected computer networks that transmit data by packet switching using a standardized Internet Protocol (IP) and many other protocols. It is made up of thousands of smaller commercial, academic, domestic and government networks. It carries various information and services, such as electronic mail, online chat, and the interlinked web pages and other documents of the World Wide Web."
        ], 
        "answer": "The Internet, or simply the Net (and often erroneously synonymous with World Wide Web), is the publicly accessible worldwide system of interconnected computer networks that transmit data by packet switching using a standardized Internet Protocol (IP) and many other protocols. It is made up of thousands of smaller commercial, academic, domestic and government networks. It carries various information and services, such as electronic mail, online chat, and the interlinked web pages and other documents of the World Wide Web.", 
        "id": "3167308"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Pets", 
        "question": "Why does my cat love vegetables?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "well, just likes the taste, my cats eat ice-cream, yogurt, fuzzies, chips, chicken, even some dog soft stuff with gravy (i think) they eat weird things too", 
            "This is a very good question, my guess is that your cat sees you eating something, and he figures that if its good for you, it must good for him too. Both of my cats are the same way, what I eat, they eat.I used to have another cat named spookers,he loved stewed tomatoes and all sorts of vegies."
        ], 
        "answer": "This is a very good question, my guess is that your cat sees you eating something, and he figures that if its good for you, it must good for him too. Both of my cats are the same way, what I eat, they eat.I used to have another cat named spookers,he loved stewed tomatoes and all sorts of vegies.", 
        "id": "1455864"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Business & Finance", 
        "question": "How much money should someone with BSc in Biochemistry and Biotechnology make?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Average out of college bio/life science job starts at around USD 30K. Assuming you have three years of experience, and if you were working for the company, you'd receive a 5% raise each year for the job well done, you're looking at $35K as target range.", 
            "Yahoo has a nice salary tool that gives you a good sense on the salary with regard to your location i the USA. . it is on the hotjobs web site under Career Tools salary"
        ], 
        "answer": "Average out of college bio/life science job starts at around USD 30K. Assuming you have three years of experience, and if you were working for the company, you'd receive a 5% raise each year for the job well done, you're looking at $35K as target range.", 
        "id": "4078125"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Business & Finance", 
        "question": "What are the factors of plant growth?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Air, Water and sunlight....", 
            "Nutrition (depends on certain soils: mixed compost, clay-like dirt, moss, bark etc.), Sunlight or other warmth, Air, Water, and depth of how far the seeds or roots are planted into the soil. Different plants require different depths when being planted."
        ], 
        "answer": "Nutrition (depends on certain soils: mixed compost, clay-like dirt, moss, bark etc.), Sunlight or other warmth, Air, Water, and depth of how far the seeds or roots are planted into the soil. Different plants require different depths when being planted.", 
        "id": "3219429"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Education & Reference", 
        "question": "How to apologize to your inferior if you were the general manager ?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Well, the best way to tell is to invite him to lunch one day and take him out and make good friends of him and eventually he might forgive and forget the mistake.. . If you dont like this then you could talk to him about it when ever you get to personally meet him.. . You could also email him saying that You did not mean exactly what went wrong, but yet making him understand that you are equal to all employess. End the email with, I have lots of confidence on the other projects he was doing and that you did not want to put pressure on him with more of the projects.", 
            "All of your questions can be handled with strategies in the book \"Make Peace With Anyone\" by David Lieberman.. . Most books of this type focus on the \"why.\" This book focuses on the \"how\" and gives step by step direction for different situations."
        ], 
        "answer": "Well, the best way to tell is to invite him to lunch one day and take him out and make good friends of him and eventually he might forgive and forget the mistake.. . If you dont like this then you could talk to him about it when ever you get to personally meet him.. . You could also email him saying that You did not mean exactly what went wrong, but yet making him understand that you are equal to all employess. End the email with, I have lots of confidence on the other projects he was doing and that you did not want to put pressure on him with more of the projects.", 
        "id": "2151788"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Business & Finance", 
        "question": "how hot is jesse mccartney to u from 1-100000?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "100000 all the way! Jesse McCartney is SOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO hot!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!", 
            "ONE OF MY FAVORITES(((THE BEST DAY OF MY LIFE))). HE DOES NOTHING FOR ME IN THE CRUSH SENSE.BUT I LIKE HIS MUSIC.  ((( A  1 ))) WHAT EVER THAT MEAN'S", 
            "about a 132 i dont find him all to my liking i prefer tatoos and pircings ;)"
        ], 
        "answer": "100000 all the way! Jesse McCartney is SOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO hot!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!", 
        "id": "67053"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Yahoo! Products", 
        "question": "how can put a question to vote?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "there is a'Call a Poll' option on your page, just below your question when you recieve more than one answer. Click that choice", 
            "click call a vote on your question page"
        ], 
        "answer": "there is a'Call a Poll' option on your page, just below your question when you recieve more than one answer. Click that choice", 
        "id": "3578579"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Food & Drink", 
        "question": "What are the rules and regulations on selling home brewed beer at bars?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "This can not be done due to sanitation laws. There has been no inspection of your brewing facility. Also the liability issue is huge if you make some one sick. Many home brew clubs share beers , but this is doen afterhouras at a bar or at a persons house.", 
            "Not quite sure but pretty sure it's illegal to make your own."
        ], 
        "answer": "This can not be done due to sanitation laws. There has been no inspection of your brewing facility. Also the liability issue is huge if you make some one sick. Many home brew clubs share beers , but this is doen afterhouras at a bar or at a persons house.", 
        "id": "3261356"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Business & Finance", 
        "question": "How can I clean a suede jacket?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "dry cleaners", 
            "Professional clean only!  You could try spot cleaning but to get it clean, you will have to have a professional do it!. That's just the way it is....sorry!"
        ], 
        "answer": "Professional clean only!  You could try spot cleaning but to get it clean, you will have to have a professional do it!. That's just the way it is....sorry!", 
        "id": "2179466"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "How do i use RUP(rational unified process) to plan my project?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Just read the RUP specifications, get sure you need iterative development and then use a lot of commom sense.", 
            "RUP stablishes a series of steps that need to be completed for the succesful completion of a project. Assign resources to every one of these stages and milestones to track the project."
        ], 
        "answer": "RUP stablishes a series of steps that need to be completed for the succesful completion of a project. Assign resources to every one of these stages and milestones to track the project.", 
        "id": "3206175"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Education & Reference", 
        "question": "What happens to Flick on the playground?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "he gets double dog dared to stick his tounge on the flag pole and he dose. he ends up getting his tounge stuck to the flag pole and is pried off by the fire department needless to say ralfy gets blamed for it", 
            "Great answer.  Vote for it."
        ], 
        "answer": "he gets double dog dared to stick his tounge on the flag pole and he dose. he ends up getting his tounge stuck to the flag pole and is pried off by the fire department needless to say ralfy gets blamed for it", 
        "id": "2799828"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Business & Finance", 
        "question": "Why is yawning contagious?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "monkey-see monkey-do. Dr. Steven M. Platek has said that we yawn b/c we are unconciously imitating other humans. (probably some kind of evolution thing) I guess there are many other species that yawn...fish, cats...(i would totally pay to see a fish yawn!).. By the way although it used to be believed that it was to get more oxygen, this, however, is not true.", 
            "bcoz when its boring our breating rate is highly reduced and the lungs push out the old content with  a strong push hence it is contagious \"BE AWARE OF IT IN CLASS ROOMS\",OK."
        ], 
        "answer": "monkey-see monkey-do. Dr. Steven M. Platek has said that we yawn b/c we are unconciously imitating other humans. (probably some kind of evolution thing) I guess there are many other species that yawn...fish, cats...(i would totally pay to see a fish yawn!).. By the way although it used to be believed that it was to get more oxygen, this, however, is not true.", 
        "id": "2744971"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "what does \"this page cannot be displayed\" mean?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "It just mean it expired just press refresh and the page will come back up", 
            "Just like it says, the page cannot be displayed. It can happen for various reasons such as the page is no longer there or the site is just down for the moment. You can try refreshing the page to see if it will come back up or try again later."
        ], 
        "answer": "Just like it says, the page cannot be displayed. It can happen for various reasons such as the page is no longer there or the site is just down for the moment. You can try refreshing the page to see if it will come back up or try again later.", 
        "id": "515027"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Computers & Internet", 
        "question": "How do I find out a guys email address?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Wel there are public directories around from where you can find the address of any friend. For this you can put his name is any search engine like yahoo and more. Its possible that it will lead you to answer youa re looking for. But please use it only for good reasons.", 
            "If you know their full name you can try Yahoo's email search page here:  http://people.yahoo.com/  Unless they have an unusual name howver you are likely to get lots of hits and may have trouble figuring out which is the right one, if any of them.  Unlike phone directorys, there really aren't any good email directories, and most people don't want their email addys out here to be harvested by some spammer, so there is little support for having an email directory."
        ], 
        "answer": "Wel there are public directories around from where you can find the address of any friend. For this you can put his name is any search engine like yahoo and more. Its possible that it will lead you to answer youa re looking for. But please use it only for good reasons.", 
        "id": "1633204"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Food & Drink", 
        "question": "how do you like your eggs?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Cooked (over easy)", 
            "Sunnyside up at home and Over Easy in a Restaurant", 
            "3 sunny side ups every morning does it for me.  I use a smiggin' of cooking spray in a non-stick pan (i know that seems redundant), and I slide the eggs out of the pan and onto my plate.  YES!!!", 
            "ScRaMbLeD!!"
        ], 
        "answer": "3 sunny side ups every morning does it for me.  I use a smiggin' of cooking spray in a non-stick pan (i know that seems redundant), and I slide the eggs out of the pan and onto my plate.  YES!!!", 
        "id": "2092685"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Science & Mathematics", 
        "question": "how to get rid of static electricity?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "If you've built up static charge on yourself and want to get rid of it, then you need to safely discharge it in a way that doesn't hurt. The best way is to touch a non-sensitive part of your body (like a knuckle) to something that's grounded (like a water faucet).. . More info on static electricity is available at the links below.", 
            "The most fun way is to touch someone who is not expecting a bit of a shock..."
        ], 
        "answer": "If you've built up static charge on yourself and want to get rid of it, then you need to safely discharge it in a way that doesn't hurt. The best way is to touch a non-sensitive part of your body (like a knuckle) to something that's grounded (like a water faucet).. . More info on static electricity is available at the links below.", 
        "id": "3747072"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Consumer Electronics", 
        "question": "how can i listen to my yahoo launchcast on my home stereo?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "Run a Stereo Patch Cable (avail. at Radio Shack) 1/8\" mini TRS to RCA right and left.  1/8\" mini plug will go into your headphone jack on puter, the other end, red plug & white plug will go into aux. input on your stereo.", 
            "good answer"
        ], 
        "answer": "Run a Stereo Patch Cable (avail. at Radio Shack) 1/8\" mini TRS to RCA right and left.  1/8\" mini plug will go into your headphone jack on puter, the other end, red plug & white plug will go into aux. input on your stereo.", 
        "id": "3089221"
    }, 
    {
        "main_category": "Health", 
        "question": "What is the bad effect of not having sex regularly?", 
        "nbestanswers": [
            "There is no known physical effects. However; there is thought to be some chemicals that are released from the brain(endorphines) I think which is a chemical that causes one to be in a more positive mood.However; if one has been sexually active and then is not( do to breaking up with partner/ can't \"get any\") one may experience the \"sexual tension\" although does not cause \"harm\" can makes ones temperment short.(ie. cranky)lol", 
            "Sexual frustration :o)", 
            "I don't know about anyone else, but I get b*tchy! ;)", 
            "there is not bad effects of not having sex regularly."
        ], 
        "answer": "There is no known physical effects. However; there is thought to be some chemicals that are released from the brain(endorphines) I think which is a chemical that causes one to be in a more positive mood.However; if one has been sexually active and then is not( do to breaking up with partner/ can't \"get any\") one may experience the \"sexual tension\" although does not cause \"harm\" can makes ones temperment short.(ie. cranky)lol", 
        "id": "1299088"
    }
]